You
Well aren't you full of surprises I
Was afraid you've forgotten about revenge, but I see you're still obsessed with family
You really want my power that badly I
Need it. I'm not strong enough. I have to go save Corrin
So come on give me every last down Sasha Romaru
Well, that's no big deal. All you had to do was ask for my help, you know, I feed off of your hate and desire for vengeance
The problem is
Taking those pills was a mistake not only do they totally kill your passion
They also enhance your curse and make it super strong. That's a dangerous combination
You can't get something for nothing if you swallow a pill and gain power. There's got to be some kind of price to pay
Just tell me what to do damn it. How can I get the strength I need to save Corrin?
Well, I'm afraid it's too late for that. There's nothing I can do to make the deceased more powerful
You're dead you your heart and other organs ruptured after taking those extra pills killing you in front of your friends
You tried to get too much power for nothing and it cost you your life
This is the end it's over no way
Then where am I now this is the afterlife what?
Unfortunately, that's not the case. I bet the afterlife is a lot better than whatever trials are in store for you
What are you saying?
Don't get me wrong your body died, but you're not at peace
Tell me why do you think that is?
Those angels are keeping you here forcibly tethered to this world
What's that not sure looks like a trumpet to me
That thing's no good stay far away from it angels can be more dangerous than demons
Hey your heart started beating that means I can repair it and make you whole again
It's better to accept me than whatever that is just forget about I can fix
I want the trumpet
Damn it an angelic horns got him hypnotized
I
Said not to touch it
Thank give me your striped Asher Amaru
Such a greedy little human can't you feel it? I've already given you the power you asked for
All those pills you took are still in effect
I'll help keep you in control that means you can safely use my power for two or three minutes
Use your time wisely you now open your eyes
He's alive
You're okay
We thought you were dead
I'm okay be back in a few
You wait
Come back
Oh come on start talking already how did you and the other humans get such strong powers who gave them to you?
We got them out of some vending machines
Remember we want to keep him alive chess he's an important hostage so make sure to handle him with king
Okay, okay, okay, I'll be gentler this time you comfortable down there
Now what kind of power is this you bastard give goren back
Come back
Impressive
Are you really a human?
Or something else?
Ashura Kanon!
Santo!
My sword gain power from my blood
Or from my blood
How was that?
You think you're tough, but I will destroy you!
Fine, you asked for it
Goren!
Oh
That was close
Why'd you come?
Get the hell out of here!
But why?
I've come this far
How is it possible I still don't have enough power to save you?
Because you're human, you're nothing more than our livestock
That's not true
You can fight all you want kid, but you could never defeat a noble like me
Shut your mouth
The only reason you exist is to feed us, to serve our every whim and make us
Shut up!
Interesting, you're even faster than before
He's gotta stop you!
Don't use any more power or the demon will take over and you'll lose control
A demon, huh?
RUIN YOU!
Get out of here now!
Shut up already!
I'm gonna save you!
Dammit you!
I told you there's no hope for me!
Don't you dare give up!
Remember, you're the one who told me to keep on living
And I finally found the person who needs my help!
Ah!
Would you listen to me?
I have everything under control right now!
I have a plan!
This isn't over yet!
You have to give me more power!
Ashuromaru!
You're not retreating?
Wow, you humans are dumb
You do realize that if you attack me again, I won't think twice about killing you, right?
Let it fill me!
More power!
Yes!
I can feel it!
Enough strength to protect my whole family!
No, stop!
Don't do this, you!
More!
All of it!
Give me all your power!
There you go, that's good
I'll give you more than you could ever imagine
Then I'll watch your desire devour you
More power, more power, more power
And then...
Stop it!
That's an order!
It'll just consume you!
Become a demon, you!
There!
Now I'm strong enough to take your head!
Go, Gesekyo!
Open the Devil's coffin on the count of nine!
No!
One...
Two...
Three...
What is that thing?
Kimizuki!
Don't get in my way, Kimizuki!
I'm gonna turn this guy to ash!
Seven...
Eight...
Hey!
Hold on!
Nine!
Undy're up!
Two...
Aand...
nosotros...
Eight...
100 00 00.
It's a normal attack then!
Long, fire up with fleets!
mysteriously like a spider- dinner!
dying and complete your mission now it worked it's okay we need to get out of
here right can't miss the transport helicopter
kimizuki what was that it's kisekyo's ability anyone who hears the nine
counts is forced into containment just temporarily and current this way
come on let's move their backup is here
nice of you to join us we've got to get to the rendezvous point i'm not losing anyone else
we're approaching nagia lord kuh we'll arrive at crowley useford's territory in a few minutes
that's not lakas's group must be from kyoto i need to find you before they arrive
major general enemy ahead damn just one i think so then we should be able to handle it
kill him and keep moving sir i thought the rest of the city was cleared one vampire won't be a
problem stay in formation we'll protect you until the enemy's been taken out
you're going to give me back my family no matter what
come on slowpokes it's time to go okay we're heading out so you guys hold down the fort all right
sure have fun
bye bye see you later lunchtime is my favorite time of day i'm so hungry my stomach's rumbling
careful now you're gonna trip over someone if you rush like that
hey you what's up can't you see that i'm reading oh come on take a break for a sec what is with you
you're being annoying if we could escape from this place what would you want to do
where would you want to go huh did you hit your head or something we can't escape because the virus
would kill us as soon as we got outside use your imagination if we could escape to the outside with
the rest of the family if we could go to a place without any vampires then don't you think we would
have fun without vampires yeah just us family sure that sounds great but it's impossible you'd be
happy yeah of course i would then i guess i'd better get busy working on that on what it's a secret
this time i'm not gonna fail you old friend
my sword drink with me
i only see one enemy eliminate him sir
more drink as much as you can
that's it i'm coming you
he's moving get ready to fight
gen wuxin
the monster has underestimated our strength and now we have him surrounded let's give the brat a spanking
this isn't real they're not gonna keep me from you
whoa not good i'll stop him
kill him while he's down
on it
oh my god
where'd this speed come from
it's up to us
no wait hold on
that boy i think he's you's family
you
i'm here
i've come for you
he's my family
i don't want to fight you michaela
listen we're you's family too
we're not giving him to you
let him go
don't worry i've got you
put him down
get your hands off of me
i know you're manipulating him
i'm gonna protect him
he's my family
that's what we do
not yours
distracting him smart move
now then die vampire
what why did you stop him
if we let them kill you
he'll be really mad at us when he wakes up
so i guess you have to take him and run
what in the hell are you doing
don't make us kill you
stand down
damn it we don't have time for this
kill him
jeez are we doing this
well we don't have much of a choice
do we
mika is you's family
which makes him our friend
and we protect our own right
keep both of them safe
stand by
but how can that be
you protect me
because you know that i'm his family
hey mika
get over here and help me keep these kids entertained
brother mika
come on brother mika
let's play
hold on
you
take him
this is your only chance
i'll clear things up with the other troops
join us at the airport and we'll leave together
join you
are you insane
there's no way
look
we don't have time to argue about this okay
i'm just gonna trust that you'll take good care of him
don't let me down
go now
you heard her let's move
this is only a temporary goodbye you
if we're lucky we'll meet again
scum
you've betrayed us
no you can't kill her
didn't you hear your commander's orders
if you can't follow them then get off the battlefield
there's no place for you here
don't look so relieved
you've got a lot of explaining to do
we're out of time
their backup is here
more vampires
damn it
no
stay back
we're dead if a noble comes
we're leaving
no way
you
Next time on Seraph of the End, you and Mika.